timelife.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Time Life

### The Site

Timelife.com (the "Site") is operated by Direct Holdings Americas Inc. StarVista is a registered trademark of Direct Holdings Americas, Inc. Time Life is a registered trademark of Time Warner Inc. or an affiliated company used under license by Direct Holdings Americas Inc., which is not affiliated with Time Inc. or Time Warner Inc. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is September 2, 2014.

### Our Privacy Policy

Direct Holdings Americas Inc. values its customers and respects their need to feel secure while shopping on our Site. We have gone to great lengths to provide a user-friendly online shopping environment that features unique products at exceptional values. Please review the information below to better understand the safeguards and policies at timelife.com. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected through this Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, then do not use the Site.

If you still have privacy concerns that you feel are not addressed in this information, please contact a Direct Holdings Americas Inc. Customer Care Representative at:

Customer Care  
StarVista Entertainment / Time Life  
P.O. Box 8788  
Pueblo, CO 81008 

This Site is not intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information submitted by visitors to the Site who are under the age of 13.

### Personal Information

We collect the personal information that you provide us while on the Site such as your name, address, email, phone number, credit and debit card numbers, and other billing information in order to complete your order, request or registration with us and/or, in the case of third party offers on the Site which you have agreed to, to enable the third parties to complete your orders with them (in which case you will be subject to such third parties' privacy policies).

When purchasing from the Site, you have the option to log in as a "Registered User" or shop as a guest. Although optional, registration allows us to personalize your shopping experience. Registration also offers a number of convenience features such as stored billing and shipping and credit card information, and allows access to members-only areas.

We may also use your email address to send you emails about hot products, specials and online promotions. From time to time, we may also use your email address to send you information about selected third party products, services or offers we think may be of interest to you. Each email you receive from us provides a link to unsubscribe to future mailings by following the unsubscribe directions that appear at the bottom of each email. If you do not want to receive emails about our offers or products or those of these selected third parties, just contact a Direct Holdings Americas Inc. Customer Care Representative via email or by phone at 1-800-950-7887, 9 AM to 9 PM, EST, seven days a week. If you are a Registered User, you can also choose not to receive marketing emails from us or these selected third parties by simply logging in and going to your Personal Profile. There you can UNCHECK the boxes giving us permission to continue emailing you about our offers or third party offers.

Please note that even if you choose not to receive marketing emails from us, you may still hear from us regarding your order status.

We may also use your name, postal delivery information and phone number to contact you offline. From time-to-time, we may also share your name and mailing address with certain direct marketing companies so that they may contact you about products, services or offers that we think would be of interest to you. If you do not wish us to contact you offline, receive such mailings, or allow us to share your information with these direct marketing companies, please contact us via email, by phone at 1-800-950-7887, 9 AM to 9 PM EST, seven days a week, or write to us at:

Customer Care  
StarVista Entertainment / Time Life  
P.O. Box 8788  
Pueblo, CO 81008 

Notwithstanding that you may have previously opted out, if you subsequently accept a third party's marketing offer on our Site, we will share your contact information (and your billing information) with that specific third party.

Direct Holdings Americas Inc. gives Registered Users the opportunity to review and update the personal information that you have provided to us by visiting your Personal Profile. Please note that deletions of your personal information or changes in your Personal Profile may not be effective immediately.

### Financial Information

We may collect your financial information such as credit and debit card numbers and bank and other financial institution account numbers in connection with transactions you enter into with Direct Holdings Americas Inc. We use your financial information to help us process these transactions and, in the case of third party offers on the Site which you have agreed to, to enable the third parties to complete your orders with them (in which case you will be subject to such third parties' privacy policies). We may use third party service providers to help us perform some of our transaction processing tasks. In such instances, we will provide your financial information to these third parties for the sole purpose of performing these tasks. We may also provide your financial information to your credit card issuer, financial institutions, credit card processors or other payment processors to process transactions. We will not be responsible or otherwise liable for any use or disclosure of your financial information by a third party to whom Direct Holdings Americas Inc. is allowed to disclose your financial information under this Privacy Policy.

### When You Ship to Another Recipient

We only collect the name(s) and postal delivery information necessary to fulfill your requests to ship to alternate addresses. We never share this information with third parties, except those third parties contractors providing fulfillment services as described above. If necessary, we may use this information to contact these individual with service issues relating to the order. We may also use these names and postal delivery information to send mailings, such as Direct Holdings catalog mailings. If you do not wish us to send these individuals such mailings, please contact us via email, by phone at 1-800-950-7887, 9 AM to 9 PM EST, seven days a week or write to us at:

Customer Care  
StarVista Entertainment / Time Life  
P.O. Box 8788  
Pueblo, CO 81008 

If you are a Registered User, you have the option to either maintain or delete contacts from your "Address Book" at any time.

### When You Use the Referral Program

When you use the referral program (the "Referral Program"), we may ask you to provide information such as your email address and your friends' email addresses. In return, you and your friends will be given the opportunity to register and become a member of the Program, and your friends will also be given the opportunity to make referrals to their friends. This feature helps us spread the word about the Program. During and after participation in the Referral Program you and/or your friends may receive additional communications from us or our vendors in relation to the Referral Program and you and/or your friends participation in it. The data collected through the Referral Program is only used for the operation and ongoing maintenance of the Referral Program and will not be distributed to any third parties other than those Direct Holdings trusted partners that may be helping us in the operation and maintenance of the Referral Program. You and your friends may opt-out of participation in the Referral Program at any time via opt-out links in all communications made to you and your friends through the Referral Program or by sending an email to [friends_optout@timelife.com](mailto:friends_optout@timelife.com)

### When You Submit a Product Review

From time to time we may provide you the opportunity to submit a review of a product offered on this Site. When you submit a product review, it may be displayed on this Site [or on other sites and media operated by Direct Holdings Americas Inc]. In addition, we may use the services of a third party (a "Third Party Operator") in order to manage the process of collecting and displaying product reviews. In that case, any review you submit may also be displayed on the site of the Third Party Operator. Please note that if a product review you submit is displayed on this Site or another site as described above, the contents of that review becomes publicly available for anyone to see. The contents of your product review displayed in this manner will be searchable using commonly available Internet search engines (such as Google and Yahoo) and may be copied and stored by anybody with access to the Internet. For these reasons you should exercise caution before you include any personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address or phone number) in the contents of any product review you submit. Direct Holdings America, Inc. takes no responsibility for any damage arising out of your including any personally identifiable information in the contents of a product review.

If we use the services of a Third Party Operator to manage product reviews, the Third Party Operator may request certain information from you before submitting a product review. For example, a Third Party Operator may request your email address for the purpose of verifying the origin of your product review. All information you submit to a Third Party Operator will be subject to the privacy policies, procedures and practices of the Third Party Operator.

### Aggregate Browsing Information

This Site may collect aggregate reporting information about Site usage. This information is used only by Direct Holdings Americas Inc. No personal or personally identifiable information is gathered or used for this process. This Site may also collect non-personally identifiable information such as your web browser type, operating system type, Internet service provider domain, or the speed of your Internet connection.

The Site uses third-party service providers to serve relevant ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on the Site. This service provider collects and uses certain anonymous information about your visits to this and other web sites to provide you with targeted advertisements for goods and services. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.

### What Are "Cookies" and How Are They Used?

To enhance your experience with the Site, we use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place on your computer to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information. However, once you choose to furnish the Site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to the Site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on the Site. We also may use cookies to display to you products, programs, or services that you may find of particular interest. We may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" (also known as "clear gifs" or "pixel tags") to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used in conjunction with cookies that conform to our cookie policy.

Third parties present on the Site, such as advertisers, may also place cookies on your browser.

If you wish to prevent cookies from being accepted, most Internet browsers allow you to do so- e.g., in Internet Explorer, click “Tools,” then “Internet Options” and adjust your cookie settings on the “Privacy” tab (e.g.: the “Block All Cookies” setting blocks all future cookies and renders all existing cookies unreadable by websites). For more information, please check your browser's technical information. Preventing your browser from accepting cookies may disable or interfere with shopping features on our sites or other sites that you may visit.

### Sale of Our Corporation

As in any business venture, the sale, merger or declaration of bankruptcy of the company is always a possibility. Should Direct Holdings Americas Inc. ever declare bankruptcy or should it or its assets ever be acquired by or merged into another organization, all customer information we have collected will be treated as an asset and may be transferred to a third party.

### Compliance with Law

We may also disclose your information when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety of Direct Holdings Americas Inc.

### Links

The Site may contain links to other sites, including, among others, those of advertisers, other third parties and companies whose trademarks may appear on the Site. We are not responsible for the information collection practices or the content of the sites to which we link.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

Direct Holdings Americas Inc. is dedicated to implementing measures to protect against the unauthorized access of your private information and providing you with a safe and secure online shopping experience. To that end, we have installed security and encryption features (Secure Socket Layer Technology).

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

### Changes to the Direct Holdings Americas Inc. Privacy Pledge

We reserve the right to update and modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your use of the Site constitutes your agreement to the policies and procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change, we will post these changes on the Site. Your use of the Site following the posting of such changes to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes on the Site. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically. You may determine when this policy was last updated by referring to the effective date found at the top of this Privacy Policy. If you have any additional questions, please contact a Direct Holdings Americas Inc. Customer Care Representative via email or call: 1-800-950-7887 from 9 AM to 9 PM EST, seven days a week.
